MATTHEW BRIDGER

Hazelwood, Beech Hill Road, Arford, Hampshire GU35 8DB 01428 481769 • 07393 175814

First Class Honours Degree Computer Science Graduate from Kent University with particular expertise in Java, React Native and a proficient understanding of Python. I continuously look for opportunities for self-improvement and apply this philosophy to my studies and life in general. I have spent 16 years in Asia which broadened my thinking. During my early education I was diagnosed with Dyslexia, while this proved challenging at the beginning, I now firmly believe this gives me a unique way of addressing challenges which differentiates me from the majority of my peers.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF KENT

BSC (HONS) 1ST - COMPUTER SCIENCES, 2019-2022

Graduated with First Class Honours Degree. Modules taken covered Algorithms, Correctness and Efficiency, Computer System, Cyber Security, Computer Networks, Game Development, Deep Learning

UDEMY

100 DAYS OF CODE: THE COMPLETE PYTHON PRO BOOTCAMP FOR 2022

Continuous development of my Python skill

ALTON COLLEGE, ALTON, HAMPSHIRE, 2017 - 2019

Extended National Diploma in Engineering – Grade - Distinction* / Distinction* / Distinction*

MORE HOUSE SCHOOL, FRENSHAM SURREY, 2004 - 2017

- IGCSE Maths Grade A
- IGCSE English Lang. Grade B
- IGCSE Physics Grade B
- IGCSE Chemistry Grade B
- IGCSE Biology Grade B
- BTEC Business Studies Grade Merit

Kellett International Secondary School, Hong Kong, 2010 - 2014 Avondale International School, Singapore, 2007 - 2010 Tanglin Trust International School, Singapore, 2004 - 2007 Duke Of Edinburgh Award – Bronze, Silver

UNIVERSITY PROJECTS

Recipe App(Group Project) - https://github.com/matthewbridger/Hello-Chef

For my 3rd year project my group made a cooking app that was tailored to help students make foods based of their fridge.

Language/Frameworks: React Native, Expo, MongoDB, Firebase, Axios, CSS, GitLab

Booking Application- https://github.com/matthewbridger/Booking-Software

In 2nd year I created an application that allows users to register and book an appointment with a Doctor. Using Java GUI the information about the booking is displayed.

Language/Frameworks: Java, MySQL, GitLab

Beach and Mountain Image Generation - https://github.com/matthewbridger/Beach-image-generation

The project GANScape is a generative adversarial network (GAN) that learns from a data set to enhance images to give them enhanced colour and definition.

Language/Frameworks: Python, TensorFlow

KEY SKILLS

Proficient:

Java

React Native

• Git

Python

Communication

Previous Experience:

CSS

SQL

• C++

EXPERIENCE AND WORK SUMMARY

THE CROWN, ARFORD, MARCH 2019 - SEP 2021

BAR STAFF March 2019 – Sept 2021

I worked part time at The Crown duties included bar work, waiting on and kitchen assistant helping to prepare food.

NOVUM STRUCTURES LIMITED - FARNHAM

CAD ASSISTANT (WORK EXPERIENCE), 2018 (11 NOVEMBER)

In November 2018 I worked at Novum Structures for 2 weeks in the Design department using FEA and 3D CAD systems. Novum are a leading designer and manufacturer of complex structural steel applications, the systems they use are a combination of powerful commercial and proprietary software systems used to optimize designs for complex building and marine applications.

TRICHORD LIMITED - FARNHAM

ASSISTANT, 2016

In 2016 I spent part of the Summer working at Trichord Sublimation Printing Company, Trichord are a leading 3D printing company working with major companies such as Vans Shoes, Vista Print and Under Armour. During my Summer with Trichord I worked with the print technicians helping to solve printing distortions when printing onto complex 3D surfaces.

INTERESTS

Keeping fit and going to the gym, my favourite hobby is mountain biking, I visit different trails most weekends with friends, it's a great form of exercise and great way to socialise with friends. I also enjoy, golf and rugby.